I was left to my own devices
我受困于自己布下的局
Many days fell away with nothing to show
苦心经营多日依然一无所获
And the walls kept tumbling down
城墙仍在崩溃瓦解
In the city that we love
在这座我们热爱的城市中
Great clouds roll over the hills Bringing darkness from above
让无尽黑暗笼罩大地狂风暴雨席卷而来
But if you close your eyes,
但若是你闭上双眼
Does it almost feel like Nothing changed at all?
是否感觉 一切依旧如昔
And if you close your eyes,
若是你闭上双眼
Does it almost feel like
是否感觉
You've been here before?
你曾经亲临此地
How am I gonna be an optimist about this?
为何我还能对一切如此乐观
We were caught up and lost in all of our vices
我们深陷于堕落的泥沼中无法自拔
In your pose as the dust settles around us
尘埃泥土将我们完全掩埋
And the walls kept tumbling down
城墙仍在崩溃瓦解
In the city that we love
在这座我们热爱的城市中
Great clouds roll over the hills Bringing darkness from above
让无尽黑暗笼罩大地狂风暴雨席卷而来
But if you close your eyes,
但若是你闭上双眼
Does it almost feel like
是否感觉
Nothing changed at all?
一切依旧如昔
And if you close your eyes,
若是你闭上双眼
Does it almost feel like
是否感觉
You've been here before?
你曾经亲临此地
How am I gonna be an optimist about this?
为何我还能对一切如此乐观